Moffat, Abbot Low; Papers apap063
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material, 1929; 1932-1943; 1; 1.30 cubic ft.
  - Press release on Assembly bills carrying out recommendations of the Joint Legislative Committee on State Fiscal Policies, 1938 February 14 (Box 1 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on Assembly bill extending New York City's emergency taxing powers, 1938 February 17 (Box 1 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on Assembly bills carrying out recommendations of the Joint Legislative Committee on State Fiscal Policies, 1938 February 19 (Box 1 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on Assembly bill requiring codification of administrative codes, rules, and regulations, 1938 February 21 (Box 1 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Address on public debt, the Association of Towns, Albany, 1938 February 23 (Box 1 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on joint resolutions concerning tax-exempt securities and extension of power to levy income tax, 1938 February 26 (Box 1 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Radio address on the work of the Assembly, WNYC, 1938 February 27 (Box 1 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on Assembly bill concerning state and local aid to local relief entities, 1938 March 16 (Box 1 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on supplemental appropriations bill, 1938 March 19 (Box 1 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on constitutional amendment permitting state compensation of automobile accident victims, 1938 April 22 (Box 1 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on constitutional amendments relating to election law, bill drafting and amendment, private and local bills, and compilation of local laws, 1938 April 29 (Box 1 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on constitutional amendments concerning eligibility for legislative office, bill drafting and amendment, and private and local bills, 1938 April 29 (Box 1 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on constitutional amendments concerning state finances, 1938 May 12 (Box 1 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on constitutional amendments concerning state and local finances, 1938 May 12 (Box 1 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on constitutional amendments concerning state and local finances, 1938 May 19 (Box 1 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on constitutional amendment concerning executive budget provisions, 1938 May 20 (Box 1 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Address on state and local finances, the Conference of Mayors, Elmira, 1938 June 9 (Box 1 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - "Municipal Fiscal Proposals before Constitutional Convention", the Bond Buyer, 1938 June 11 (Box 1 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Published version of the speech given at the Conference of Mayors, 1938 June 9 (Box 1 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Letter to the delegates of the Constitutional Convention, 1938 June 20 (Box 1 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Radio address on state finance issues before the Constitutional Convention, WQXR, 1938 June 24 (Box 1 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
    One copy contains extensive handwritten annotations.
  - Address on the work of the Legislature, Third Metropolitan Realty Conference, 1939 January 11 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on slum clearance bill, 1939 January 19 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Letter to Joseph McGinnies concerning local government indebtedness, 1939 January 24 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on joint legislative budget hearing, 1939 January 31 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Amendment of joint rules concerning home rule, 1939 February 1 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on responsibility for budget deficit, 1939 February 1 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Bills introduced and bills killed by Assembly Ways and Means Committee, 1939 February 2 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Letter to Fiorello LaGuardia on New York Housing Authority bond financing, 1939 February 6 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on bill extending New York City Council's power to grant partial tax exemptions to owners of repaired or renovated buildings, 1939 February 8 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Letter to Perley A. Pitcher concerning the Constitution and local government, 1939 February 8 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on Assembly bill calling for codification and prompt publication of administrative rules and codes, 1939 February 13 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on New York City occupancy tax and bond financing and letter to Fiorello LaGuardia, 1939 February 16 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on opposition to Governor's tax program, 1939 February 19 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on Assembly budget hearing, 1939 February 20 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on bills implementing Constitution in the field of local finance, 1939 February 20 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on Assembly budget hearing, 1939 February 21 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - List of individuals present at budget hearing, 1939 February 22 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - List of speakers at budget hearing, 1939 February 22 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - List of speakers at Assembly budget hearing, 1939 February 24 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on bills reported favorably by the Assembly Ways and Means Committee, 1939 February 28 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Radio address on housing legislation, WNYC, 1939 March 3 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on investigation of relief programs, 1939 March 6 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on Assembly bill revising the State Finance Law, 1939 March 8 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on Assembly bill concerning radio broadcasters and libel and slander actions, 1939 March 9 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on Senate bill establishing a separate sinking fund for redemption of New York City transit unification bonds, 1939 March 12 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on Assembly bill establishing a temporary state commission to revise statutes concerning municipal finances, 1939 March 13 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on bills reported favorably by the Assembly Ways and Means Committee, 1939 March 14 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - "Copies of Letters from the Federal Emergency Administration and the Reconstruction Finance Corporation re. Proposed Brooklyn-Battery Bridge", 1939 March 15; 1939 March 22 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on joint conference of the Senate Finance and Taxation Committees and the Assembly Ways and Means Committee, 1939 April 16 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on printing of the main budget, 1939 April 19 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Speech in Assembly on appropriations, 1939 April 27 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - "Bills Reported by Assembly Ways and Means Committee", 1939 May 2 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on introduction of Assembly bills reducing spending, 1939 May 4 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on implementation of legislative appropriations bills, 1939 May 10 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Remarks in Assembly on the Governor's message, 1939 May 12 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on memorial to the U.S. Congress concerning hospitalization of mentally ill aliens, 1939 May 18 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on "New Revenues Provided and Special Appropriations Bills Passed by the Legislature of 1939", 1939 May 22 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on New York City proposals to eliminate kindergartens, 1939 June 13 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on projected budget surplus, 1939 June 20 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on special legislative session necessitated by Court of Appeals ruling on departmental budget cuts, 1939 June 21 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Address to Assembly on Governor's [budget?] message, 1939 June 23 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Letter to members of the Senate Finance and Assembly Ways and Means Committees, 1939 June 26 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on Assembly bill barring elimination of kindergartens and evening schools, 1939 June 30 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on Assembly supplemental appropriations bill, 1939 July 10 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Extract from New York Herald Tribune article, "Lehman Asks Political Truce in Emergency", 1939 September 8 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on letter sent to members of the Assembly Ways and Means Committee, 1939 October 14 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Charts and tables concerning state debt, 1939 October 14 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release in response to statements of Fiorello LaGuardia, 1939 October 18 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on dispute with Fiorello LaGuardia, 1939 October 20 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Department of Taxation and Finance collection data, 1939 October 20 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - "Appropriations by New York State and Federal Government", 1939 November 1 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - "Time Limitations on Contracting Housing Indebtedness", 1939 November 22 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - "Analysis of Fiscal Action by Governor and Legislature by Departments", 1939 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - "Appropriation Bills Passed and New Revenue Provided by the Legislature of 1939 and Signed by the Governor" (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - "Effect of Tax on Real Estate ($1.00 per Thousand) as Compared with a Ten Percent Reduction in State Aid for Education", 1939 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - "Summary of Reductions", 1939 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - "Summary of Supplemental Bill; Legislature of 1939" (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on Assembly budget hearing, 1940 January 25 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on Assembly Ways and Means Committee analysis of the Governor's budget, 1940 February 4 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on Assembly bill extending municipalities' ability to receive federal WPA and PWA funds, 1940 February 7 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on Assembly budget hearing, 1940 February 7 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on Assembly bill extending New York City's emergency taxing powers, 1940 February 15 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on Assembly bills affecting the Division of Housing and the Public Housing Law, 1940 February 16 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on Assembly bills amending the General Municipal Law, 1940 February 21 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Address on state aid to localities, the Association of Towns, 1940 February 21 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on legislative cuts in the Governor's budget, 1940 February 28 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Remarks in Assembly concerning the Governor's message on revision of the budget, 1940 March 4 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on bills reported by the Assembly Ways and Means Committee, 1940 March 4 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on Assembly bills concerning the unification of the New York City transit system, 1940 March 11 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on Assembly bills concerning billboards, 1940 March 12 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on Assembly hearing on the Shaver canal constitutional amendment, 1940 March 12 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on Assembly Ways and Means Committee appropriations bills, 1940 March 13 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on Assembly bill on the notarization of income tax returns, 1940 March 20 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Statement concerning the Governor's message on grade crossing elimination, 1940 March 20 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on Assembly bill allowing diversion of emergency relief tax monies to certain welfare purposes, 1940 March 24 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on constitutional amendment concerning grade crossing bonds, 1940 March 25 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on New York City emergency relief tax bill, 1940 March 26 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on Assembly bills concerning New York City and the bank tax, 1940 March 26 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on Assembly supplemental appropriations bill, 1940 March 26 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on Assembly bill concerning revision of the Finance Law, 1940 March 26 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on the Legislature's fiscal plan for 1940-41, 1940 April 1 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - List of funds allocated [?] to commissions and legislative committees, 1940 May 1 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Tables of fiscal plans, 1940 May 1 (Box 2 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Address on state regulation of municipal finance, the Conference of Mayors, Rochester, 1940 June 11 (Box 3 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Remarks made before Jewish War Veterans, New York County Council Installation, New York City, 1940 June 20 (Box 3 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Address on "The Constitution and Municipal Debt", New York State Bar Association, Saranac Lake [?], 1940 June 28 (Box 3 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on the relationship between sound management of municipal government and national defense, 1940 June 28 (Box 3 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - "Proposed $60,000,000 Highway-Parkway Bond Issue", 1940 August 21 (Box 3 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Radio address on "Campaign Issues-Taxation", WQXR, 1940 September 13 (Box 3 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Address on the budget and appropriations, Albany Chapter of the National Association of Cost Accountants, Albany, 1940 September 18 (Box 3 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - "Proposed Constitutional Amendment for a $60,000,000 Highway-Parkway Bond Issue", 1940 September 23 (Box 3 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Radio address on national defense and Wendell Wilkie campaign, WQXR, 1940 September 30 (Box 3 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Address on state and local fiscal relationships, City Affairs Committee, New York City, 1940 December 7 (Box 3 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on cost of gubernatorial inaugurations, 1940 December 10 (Box 3 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on letter to Herbert H. Lehman, 1940 December 11 (Box 3 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on constitutional amendment allowing the Legislature to prohibit further issuance of grade crossing bonds, 1941 January 13 (Box 3 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on budget hearing, 1941 February 5 (Box 3 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on bill regulating billboards, 1941 February 7 (Box 3 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Speakers list for executive budget hearing, 1941 February 12 (Box 3 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Seating list for budget hearing, 1941 February 12 (Box 3 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on Assembly bills concerning municipal finance, 1941 February 19 (Box 3 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on constitutional amendment allowing the Legislature to establish tax stabilization reserves, 1941 February 24 (Box 3 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Remarks in Assembly concerning quarterly payment of income tax, 1941 March 4 (Box 3 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on Assembly bills concerning municipal finance, 1941 March 4 (Box 3 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on Assembly bill concerning the repayment of appropriations made to the Power Authority, 1941 March 8 (Box 3 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on Assembly bill extending the power of cities to impose a one percent utilities tax for unemployment relief, 1941 March 8 (Box 3 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on Assembly bill allowing the escheating of funds on deposit with federal courts, 1941 March 9 (Box 3 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on procedure for the purchase of New York City buses and subway cars, 1941 March 11 (Box 3 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Remarks in Assembly on the budget, 1941 March 12 (Box 3 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on bill granting a tax exemption to the Metropolitan Opera House, 1941 March 16 (Box 3 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Letter from New York City Comptroller Joseph D. McGoldrick, 1941 March 21 (Box 3 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on policy changes remedying New York City's financial problems, 1941 March 31 (Box 3 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on bill allowing the budget surplus to be used for defense emergencies, 1941 March 31 (Box 3 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on statement of Republican fiscal policies, 1941 March 31 (Box 3 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on the supplemental budget, 1941 April 1 (Box 3 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on Governor's veto of legislation allowing the state to take over abandoned condemnation awards to unknown owners, 1941 May 15 (Box 3 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Address on welfare legislation, National Conference of Social Work, Atlantic City, 1941 June 5 (Box 3 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on budget surplus, 1941 July 4 (Box 3 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Address on $60,000,000 diversion amendment, Tenth Assembly District Republican Club, New York City, 1941 October 30 (Box 3 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on Assembly bill allowing quarterly payment of income tax, 1941 December 1 (Box 3 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on analysis of proposal to allow deduction of federal income taxes when determining state taxable income, 1941 December 18 (Box 3 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on issuing of the Green Book, 1941 December 24 (Box 3 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on bill defining the length of the war emergency, 1942 January 7 (Box 3 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Letter to Assembly members from Speaker Oswald D. Heck concerning Assembly rules, 1942 January 8 (Box 3 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on bill permitting quarterly payment of income tax, 1942 January 8 (Box 3 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on Assembly bill changing the date of the final lapsing of appropriations, 1942 January 8 (Box 3 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on Assembly bill extending New York City's emergency taxing power, 1942 January 9 (Box 3 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - List of certificates of intent executed since the close of the last legislative session, 1942 January 12 (Box 3 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on Assembly bills concerning municipal borrowing, 1942 January 13 (Box 3 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release [?] on establishment of Assembly Committee on Local Finance, 1942 January 13 (Box 3 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on Assembly bill granting income tax exemptions to non-resident military personnel stationed in New York State, 1942 January 16 (Box 3 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))
  - Press release on Assembly bills allowing quarterly payment of income tax, 1942 January 23 (Box 3 (1-Press Releases, Speeches, and Reference Material))